Register of the Senegalese Subject Collection, 1953-2001
Hoover Institution Archives
Senegalese Subject Collection,
1953-2001
XX831
4 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (3 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Electronic bulletins, pamphlets, serial issues, reports, and other printed matter, relating to political, social and economic conditions in Senegal.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Senegal.; Africa.
Series Description
- SUBJECT FILE, 1953-1994 (Box 1)
  Brochures, bulletins, newsletters, pamphlets, printed matter, reports and serial issues relating to economic, political and social conditions in Senegal
- DROUGHT AND FAMINE, 1973-1994 (Box 1)
  Newsletter, printed matter, program, report and serial issues relating to the drought conditions in Senegal
- REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENTS, 1978-1994 (Box 1)
  Clippings, manuel, newsletter and printed matter relating to the revolutionary movements in Senegal
Container List
See card catalog for increments that may have been received after December 1994
- SUBJECT FILE, 1953-1994
  - General (Box 1)
  - Elections
  - Health
  - Religion
  - Women
- DROUGHT AND FAMINE, 1973-1994
  - Newsletter, printed matter, program, report and serial issues relating to the drought conditions in Senegal (Box 1)
- REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENTS, 1978-1994
  - Mouvement pour le Parti du Travail (Box 1)
  - Parti Communiste
  - Union des Travailleuvrs Libres du Senegal
- Incremental materials (Box 2-5)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described.